elks.org 2008-12-18

# The Benevolent & Protective Order of Elks of the USA

**Elks.Org Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy lets you know how the personal information that you submit to the Elks.Org web site is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Policy. The following policies are in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, message boards and opt-in announcement lists operated by the Elks.Org web site. Other Departments, Committees, Associations, and Lodges of the Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks may have different Policies. 

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers called an "IP address." When a visitor requests a page from the Elks.Org web site, our web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate. We also use "cookies" to track individual usage patterns on the Elks.org web site. Our web servers do NOT record e-mail addresses of our visitors. 

**What are cookies?**

From time to time, Elks.Org may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of the Elks.Org's web site you have visited or customized, and to confirm your identity when visiting restricted-access pages. 

**What other information do you request?**

During our registration process we request your email address as well as additional "off-line" contact information. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy, that means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party without your consent. 

In addition, Elks.Org will not send you email that you have not agreed to receive. We may from time to time send e-mail announcing new Elks.Org services. 

**Credit Card Transactions**

For security purposes, Elks.org donations and other credit card transactions are processed by [Authorize.net](http://www.authorize.net/), a company that specializes in highly secure credit card transactions conducted via the Internet. Credit card numbers are NOT stored on the Elks.org servers, and are not available for future transactions. Credit card numbers and other transaction details are not shared with any company or organization other than [Authorize.net](http://www.authorize.net/), which maintains its own strict privacy policy. 

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**

Elks.Org will disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

1) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on the Elks.Org web site or the Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks, 

2) Protect and defend the rights or property of the Elks.Org web site or the Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks, or the visitors of the Elks.Org web site, 

3) Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties, 

4) Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities. 

Elks.Org uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties which receive the information. Elks.Org also links to a wide variety of other sites and contains advertisements of third parties. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy. 

**Your Consent To This Agreement**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by the Elks.Org web site as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

By using our web site, you agree to indemnify and hold harmless the B.P.O. Elks of the USA, Inc., from any claim, demand or expense arising out of your use of the website except for occurences caused by the sole negligence of the B.P.O. Elks of the USA, Inc.
